jakub havlík

address: Donaustraße 49, 12043, Berlin

email: havlik9@gmail.com phone: 015752835747

linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jakubhavlik/

github: https://github.com/nine-chairs

website: https://nine-chairs.github.io/portfolio-website/

web-dev skills:

HTML
CSS
JavaScript / jQuery
Mongo DB
Express
React / React Native / Redux
Angular
Node.js
PostgreSQL
REST APIs
Git / Github
TDD

featured projects:

Adobe CS

Listapeli: A full-stack MEAN application allowing users to save data about their favorite movies. Designed both the client-side (Angular) and the server-side (REST API and database). (link)

Meet-app: A serverless, progressive web application (PWA) built with React using a test-driven development (TDD) technique. The application uses the Google Calendar API to fetch upcoming events. (link)

Chata-pp: A chat application for mobile devices built using React Native. The app provides users with a chat interface and options to share images and their location. (link)

Gotta search'em all: A small web application built with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that loads data from an external API and enables the viewing of data points in detail. (link)

statement:

As a full-stack web developer, I would like to be a mediator between the user experience and the functional logic. In addition to my leveled-up web-dev skills, I can offer 4 years of professional experience as an architect / urban planner. From my architectural background, I can bring the ability to combine functionality with aesthetics as well as systematic thinking and problem-solving skills.

work experience:

2022 – 2022 Freelance Web Developer @ Nine Chairs

2020 – 2021 Laboratory for Visionary Architecture, Berlin, DE (architect)

2019 – 2020 IPR Praha (Planning Institute of Prague), Prague, CZE (urban planner)

2017 – 2020 Needlab, Barcelona, ESP (researcher / architect)

2017 – 2018 Paulíny Hovorka Architekti, B. Bystrica, SVK (architect)

education:

2021 – 2022 Career Foundry, Berlin, DE (full-stack web-dev bootcamp)

2015 – 2017 Institute for Advanced Architecture, Barcelona, ESP (master's degree)

2014 - 2014 CEPT University, Ahmedabad, IND, (exchange program)

2010 - 2015 Academy of Fine Arts and Design, Bratislava, SVK (bachelor's degree)

language skills:

Slovak: native Czech: native

English: fluent (CAE, IELTS)

German: fluent Spanish: fluent

Portuguese: intermediate

other things I enjoy:

illustration – https://www.instagram.com/_supersilla/ photography – https://www.instagram.com/jakub___havlik/ urbanism – https://issuu.com/jakubhavlik playing drums in this band – https://sptfy.com/KdVD playing concerts with that band – https://tinyurl.com/ywwsnkeh